Eryn Craig

Web Developer

Los Angeles, CA 90045

206.319.8300 erynlcraig@gmail.com

Experienced web developer with background in design, team leadership, and customer service. Excels at web design and git version control, organized programming, communication with employers, clients, and coworkers, and building web and mobile apps. Trained in full stack development including CSS, HTML, Javascript, database structure and more. Very open to learning new languages and technology. Open to remote work or relocation.

Portfolio: https://darkfather63.github.io/Portfolio-Website/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/eryncraig/

Skills

Languages: HTML5, CSS, Javascript, SQL, and more **Frameworks**: React, React Native, Angular, Bootstrap, Sass

Relational Databases: PostgreSQL, mySQL

NoSQL: MongoDB, Firebase **Cloud:** AWS, Google Cloud, Heroku

Process styles and tools: Github, Test-Driven Development, Object-Oriented Dev, API

configuration, AJAX, JSON, UNIX CLI, Linux, responsive design. **Other:** Adobe, Data Visualization, Research, Problem solving

Experience

Freelance / Web Designer, Developer

JUNE 2018 - PRESENT, SEATTLE WA

• Collaborated with clients in person and via website on custom pieces and domains,

Seattle Art Museum / Security Supervisor

JUNE 2019 - AUGUST 2021, SEATTLE, WA

 Contributed input on functionality, accessibility, and success of curation of galleries on a monthly basis, as well as reporting any incidents and monitoring security systems.

Sunrise Medical Billing / Billing Specialist

JUNE 2014 - JUNE 2018, VANCOUVER, WA

• Balanced accounts, troubleshooted billing and code errors, maintained web accounts and services. Improved clientele by 80%.

Education

CareerFoundry / Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development

MARCH 2022 - OCTOBER 2022, BERLIN, GERMANY

Training in Full Stack Web Development via immersion, including Javascript, React, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, MERN stack technology, server side programming and more.

University of Washington / B.S. in Arts and Art History

SEPTEMBER 2017 - JUNE 2019, SEATTLE, WA

Development

myFlix Web Application:

Worked as a full stack developer and designer of a MERN web application for public use. Development included configuring an API, developing a search engine for a database of films, and designing and building the user interface based on user stories.